[
    {
        "back": "none",
        "front": "Aucun",
        "bd": "None"
    },
    {
        "back": "education",
        "front": "Accès à l'école",
        "bd": "CTR4_Note_Ecole"
    },
    {
        "back": "soins",
        "front": "Accès aux soins",
        "bd": "CTR2_Note_Medecin"
    },
    {
        "back": "festival",
        "front": "Ville festive",
        "bd": "CTR5_Note_Festival"
    },
    {
        "back": "logement",
        "front": "Coût du logement",
        "bd": "CTR1_Note_loyer"
    },
    {
        "back": "gare",
        "front": "Proximité d'une gare",
        "bd": "CTR3_Note_Gare"
    },
    {
        "back": "musee",
        "front": "Musées présents",
        "bd": "CTR6_Musee"
    },
    {
        "back": "association",
        "front": "Ville associative",
        "bd": "CTR7_Associations"
    },
    {
        "back": "chomage",
        "front": "Dynamisme économique",
        "bd": "CTR9_Dynamisme_Economique"
    },
    {
        "back": "fibre",
        "front": "Ville fibrée",
        "bd": "CTR8_Acces_Fibre"
    },
    {
        "back": "soleil",
        "front": "Ensoleillement",
        "bd": "CTR10_Ensoleillement"
    },
    {
        "back": "securite",
        "front": "Sécurité",
        "bd": "CTR11_Securite"
    }
]